This is the weather forecast for the
Tokyo area, as released at 1 PM...
...by the Meteorological Agency's
Forecasting Department.
As of 11 AM on the 21st, the large
and powerful Typhoon 32...
...was in the southernmost parts
of Shizuoka Prefecture...
...heading northeast
at speeds of 45kph.
Everyone is advised to
use extreme caution...
Its winds are presently in
the 54kph range...
...and caution is advised for the
Tokyo Metropolitan Area...
Let's chase our dreams...
... holding hearts burning...
... like the summer sunshine.
If we have courage...
... at 100 miles an hour...
... I'm sure the door will open.
Since sadness is the road
that leads to smiles...
... dull, dingy shoes will
start to shine, too.
The most wonderful dream
in the world...
The pounding beat speeds up.
The eyes are prisms that
catch the wind...
... and in the voices of
countless friends...
... I feel happiness.
TOKYO TYPHOON RALLY
Oh, man, I've had it. It's been
like this every week this year.
Nothing we can do about it. We're up
against Mother Nature, after all.
Oooh! This summer I was sure I was
gonna lose a little more weight...
...take on a 1-kg parfait, heft the
Sumida Festival palanquin...
...and at the night stalls, buy apple candy
and fried octopus balls in seaweed...
...and baked corn and
fresh radish pickles...
...and go goldfish-catching and balloon
dart-throwing and target shooting...
...and shelltops... and then, uh,
brown sugar candy, oh, hey!
Okay, okay. We're moving.
Aw, there's no point
to anything now...
Hmh? Miyuki, pull
over to the left.
Huh? Okay...
Students of Wakaba Preschool, please
go straight home immediately.
Don't go anywhere else. There's
a scary typhoon on the way.
Wow! It's Natsumi!
It's Miyuki!
Hey!
What's with this "Natsumi" stuff?
That's "Miss Natsumi" to you!
Well, your name is
Natsumi, right?
Ri-ight?
It's enough for us to call
you Natsumi, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, hey, Miyuki, do you know where
there's an animal hospital?
Huh? A vet? I'm not sure if
there is one in this area...
You don't even know that?
Some policewoman
you are.
Huh? Isn't that Chibi?
You sure got big.
Preschool
Do you know this
cat, Natsumi?
Hey, how do you know?
Huh?
There is nothing that Natsumi the hero
doesn't know. Are you impressed?
You can't
fool us with that.
Don't
belittle the masses!
What's going on? Are you
keeping her, Maho?
Uh-uh. She came to the preschool
a little while ago.
She's not feeling well. She
doesn't eat anything.
So that's why you wanted to take
her to the hospital, huh?
Uh-huh.
I get it now.
Oh, it's Ken!
Kennie's here! Kennie's here!
Kennie's on his motorcycle!
Kennie! Kennie! Kennie!
Oh, so Nakajima is "Kennie"
around here?
Sort of...
What's this? She's
awfully fat...
Stop that! You've got
to hold her properly.
Oh, uh, I see...
All right, we'll see that
she's taken care of.
Will she be okay?
We'll take care of it. We promise.
So you all hurry home. Go on!
Look out!
Hey! Where'd you learn to drive?! Don't
mess around like that, you idiot!
Natsumi's scary!
That Lancia... it's
got to be!
Umm... Nakajima...
I'm now going to catch
that ill-mannered car!
So take care, everyone!
Oh, he fell over!
That GSX...
I see, I see. I knew it all the time,
uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, cut it out, Natsumi. You're
just jeering at us both.
You're no better than
those preschoolers.
Thanks to whom, we blew our
chance to catch that Lancia!
Well, well, nice change of subject.
Won't work on me, though.
Natsumi!
Welcome back!
You're done for the day, right?
Yeah. We've done
our nightshift.
Hey, hey, Nakajima's looking
a little funny.
You know anything
about it?
Oh! Not you too, Yoriko!
Something DID happen,
didn't it!
It sure did!
I guess this will do for now.
But you know, Nakajima
didn't look at all happy.
He just went and locked
himself in the morgue.
I bet he was just blushing.
Oh!
Are you gonna have kittens?
Eh?!
Oh, yeah! Her breasts are big!
That's why she's so listless!
So that's it!
Kobayakawa!
I need to ask you something.
Please come!
Uh... Okay.
Hey, hey, "something
to ask" must be!
A proposal. It's got to be!
Who'd have thought they'd
have gotten that close!
It's a big scoop.
We're tagging along, right?
Oh, let's.
All right!
The rain's pouring down so loud, I can't
hear what they're talking about at all.
Who cares what they're talking about?
It's actions that matter!
Go! Go get 'er, Nakajima!
You're the only one I can
ask this of. I beg you!
For something like that,
I'll gladly assist you.
And besides, there are a couple others
who look like they'll help... right?
Natsumi! Bring that toolbox!
Uh, right!
Yoriko! There's an auxiliary flashing
light and radio! Bring them here!
Uh, right!
Natsumi, I need a speaker too!
Huh? Where is it?
On the highest shelf in the back!
Okay, here you go.
Now get me some grease.
Uh, right, right!
I'm pooped.
Here.
Thanks.
Thanks for doing
this all for me...
Uh-uh, no problem. I can't do
anything useful anyway...
But I'm a little disappointed,
you know?
So this is what your request turned
out to be? Oh, and we were sure...
Huh? What did you
think it was?
Eh? Uh, well, um...
Never mind that.
Are you really going to go out there
using a..."KLE," was it...
...as a police motorcycle?
Even you wouldn't stand a chance in
the middle of a typhoon like this.
I know it's risky. I have
my reasons...
What condition are
the victims in?
I don't know, but the ambulance
should already be on its way.
Tell Nakajima that the
bike's finished.
And see that the cat gets fed.
Cat food and water, right?
I used to enjoy typhoons,
you know?
Now we can't just enjoy
them, can we?
Mini Patrol Four calling Bokuto Station!
How long before the ambulance arrives?
Well... the roads are badly flooded,
and it seems to be taking a detour.
Looks like it'll take another
ten minutes or so.
Roger! We'll figure something
out! Miyuki!
I know!
It's gonna be all right now.
Natsumi! Hurry!
It's locked! Hang on a sec!
Wha?!
Now that it's come to this...
...we can only exercise
brute force!
Here we go...
DIAMOND KNUCKLE ATTACK!
I'm through.
Oh wow!
The watermelons are
all taken care of.
Nice going. Here.
Thanks.
So what was the cause?
Well, you see...
A Lancia Delta? Then the
one this afternoon?
Probably... in which case, it's
just as Nakajima feared...
Eh? What does "Kennie"
have to do with it? Ow...
It seems it appears every year at this
time, only on days with typhoons...
...a legendary car that runs through
town like it owned the place.
Then, you mean, a year ago?
Yes... through some
happenstance...
...Nakajima met up with
and challenged it.
And he lost, huh?
The bike was a serious handicap! He
was up against four-wheel drive.
And it was outfitted for rallying. Not
even Nakajima could beat that!
So that's why he wanted the KLE 500
with foul-weather outfitting.
That's Nakajima for you; he doesn't
like to lose, does he?
It's not just that. The Lancia's reckless
driving escalates each year.
Fact is, it didn't cause any accidents
up until last year.
If left alone at the rate it's
going, next we'll have...
Yes, this is Mini Patrol
Four. Go ahead.
Natsumi, Miyuki, I don't know
what to do. Hurry back here!
It won't eat, it makes weird high-pitched
cries... It just won't settle down!
Aren't its kittens about
to be born?
If so, it wouldn't be crying.
Besides, it looks like
it's in a lot of pain.
I thought of calling a veterinarian,
but there's all the wind and rain...
We can't very well wait for the typhoon
to pass. Natsumi! Get things ready!
All right! Leave it to me!
Where? Say again!
Saitoo Animal Hospital, 7-4
Morishita-cho, Sumida-ku.
They stop examining patients at five,
but they said they'd have a look.
Roger.
Animal hospital? What
are those two up to?
This is Bokuto Station.
Go ahead.
Yoriko? What are Kobayakawa
and Tsujimoto doing?
Oh, Nakajima, you see...
Blackout!
People will start mobbing the phone
lines. Get someone on it!
The circuit's holding!
Hey! Yoriko!
Looks like a breech birth. On top of
which, her pelvis seems narrow.
Well, what do we do?
I'm sorry, but with things the
way they are right now...
Not much you can do in
a blackout, is there?
Let me see if I can contact the
Veterinarians' Association.
I think there'll be a place somewhere
that will take her in.
Please!
We didn't hear anything about a blackout.
Tell us these things ahead of time!
Sorry. But things were all messed up
here, too. They still are, though...
Where was that hospital
the vet referred us to?
Ayase, in Adachi-ku. We can work it out
if we get to the Kosuge Interchange.
Oh, Capital Expressway Six is
closed due to construction!
Why you! You should tell us
things like that beforehand!
Aww, it happened
three days ago!
If it's closed, that means no
one's driving on it... right?
Is... that so?!
Mini Patrol Four is now en route to Ayase.
We will be taking Capital Expressway Six!
What! Are you serious? That's...
Over and out! So long!
ENTRANCE
NO TRESPASSING
Bokuto Police Station
The wind's really hellacious!
Feels like we're gonna
get swept away!
Driving in this rain and crosswind
is a life-threatening proposition.
If you're getting out, do it now.
Looking to get it all to yourself?
That's not fair.
This is where the fun begins.
Roger!
We're almost there. Hang on!
What's this?
What do you mean?
I thought it was a little bit strange, to see
such a gentle expression on your face.
What're you talking about?
It's much stranger for you to be doing
something this outrageous!
That makes us even, huh?
What is it?
There's a car behind us!
No way!
What the?! It's that Lancia Delta!
I know!
Of all the times it could
pick to show up!
He's not likely to let us
go by quietly, is he?
He's out of his mind! Miyuki, blow
him away with the nitro!
That's impossible in
these conditions!
It's too dangerous with this wind
and this poor visibility!
Besides...
Oh, yeah. There's no telling
whether Chibi could take it.
Miyuki! Get off at Tsutsumi Avenue!
Huh?
Let the Lancia Delta
pass us by.
At this rate, he'll mess
you up, Miyuki!
Even if he follows us, we'll have the edge
down below. We'll figure something out.
You're right.
He's got us figured! He's
not going to let us off!
Goddamn!
He's a little better than I am.
Miyuki...
What do we do?
Mini Patrol Four, do
you read me?
Nakajima?!
Where are you, Nakajima?!
Right in front of you.
Yoriko filled me in.
You're carrying a patient, so you must
be having a hard time fighting him.
I'll back you up.
Kennie! You're so cool!
Stop that.
I'm the one who's taking you
on! Come and get me!
Kobayakawa! It's only
5 km to Kosuge!
Get into his slipstream and follow us!
His car should act as a windbreak!
Will you be all right, Nakajima? Bikes are
the most dangerous in this weather!
I put my faith in this bike
you tuned, Kobayakawa.
Oh, man! We've already reached
the Kosuge offramp!
Hey, hey, Miyuki, you've fallen for
"Kennie" all over again, I bet.
Look, I told you to stop referring
to him like that.
Well, how about Kenbo? Ken-Ken?
Kensuke? The Kenster?
"Kennie" really is best,
don't you think?
Oh! It's from "Kennie!"
This is where we
part for now.
I'll join you after I take
care of this clown.
Take care of that
chubby Chibi.
I wonder if he can win out.
Sure he can! He will! Kennie
can if anyone can!
Natsumi! You keep saying, "Kennie,
Kennie," and now I'm doing it, too...
What's wrong with that? You're gonna
be calling him that sooner or later!
How can you say that! Don't decide
such things by yourself!
Whatever! Keep your
eyes on the road!
Don't try to evade the subject!
We're gonna crash!
I repeat...
...the Joban Line is currently halted
within the Tokyo city limits.
It is unclear when service
will be reestablished.
Right at the next corner. Then
left about 300m after that!
Roger!
Hang in there! It's just
a little longer!
You bastard!
Ah-ah!
I'm not like I was last year!
We can't get through here!
Where's a detour?
Hold on... Back up and go left on that last
road... no good! Neither is going right!
Which way?
Mmm... there is no way.
Eh?! It can't be!
With this much water, it's all the same
no matter which way you go!
Getting around this will mean
going way out of our way.
Which means we only have one option
left... Natsumi, you're on!
I had a feeling it would
come to this.
All set. Natsumi, this
is the final hurdle.
No problem. My bike technique
can stand up to this typhoon!
Yeah!
Go!
I've got something to say
to you. Listen up!
When driving near children,
maintain a safe distance...
...and furthermore, go slowly!
Remember that.
"Animal Hospital"
"This is a present for good children.
Pick it up gently."
"Miss Natsumi, Miss Miyuki,
Thank You"
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
... I will protect you from sighs.
The sunset skyline flashes past
in my side-view mirror.
This is the road I drive on every day,
believing in my dreams.
On rainy days, windy days, and days
when I wanted to throw it all away...
... you smiled as you
sat beside me.
I love the unchanging vista, the sky
that we watch together.
That's why I'm confident that I can
hang in there, if it's for you.
I love the smile you always have.
With all the passion I have...
... I will protect you from sighs.
I love this town where we
happened to meet...
Honestly, those kids... Miyuki,
this isn't coming off!
Look, just put some elbow
grease into it.
We'll clean her up even
if it takes all day.
Eek! No way!
THE TRUTH BEHIND
THE RUMORS
Why are you having a matchmaking, when
you have someone like Nakajima?
Want me to tell?
Hey, who are you talking about?
Stop her, Nakajima! You're the
only one who can stop Miyuki!
Look, what are you
talking about?
Wanna know?
You want her to be taken away by
some nobody from nowhere?
How did you come up
with a story like that?
Shall I tell you?
So you're the cause of all this!
You're Under Arrest, File 3,
"Love's Highway Stars."
LOVE'S HIGHWAY STARS